[{"answer": "Well, what passengers are telling us is that they - it was just a normal day at the airport when suddenly, they heard very, very loud popping.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "Kyung what do we know about exactly what happened today?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "That is absolutely correct.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "Is that the correct position?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yeah, Piers, we're starting to get a better picture him, if not his recent life out in Los Angeles and certainly is what growing up here on the east coast in his background here with his family standing outside of his dad's home near in Pennsville, the police have been here for most of the night now.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "What else have we learned?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "I don't know, the only indication I have was from a gentlemen I wrote in the bus with through the holding area who said he saw the shooter from down that hallway and it was a large rifle, it had a scope and this gentlemen that I talked to believe that there was a red dot from that scope that moved across his chest, and the chest of the people around him, other than that one account, your guess or you're reporting and certainly is as good as mine.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Did you have any indication from people you talked to?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Well, I was going to board on flight to Philadelphia.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "When this started you heard these bullets going off and this guy shooting indiscriminately, what was going through your head?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "I feel extremely grateful and I feel angry that this feels like Ground Hog Day and, you know, there's -- everyone's always saying it's too soon to have a discussion about Assault Rifles, well I just went through trauma and I think that right now is not too soon.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "I mean how do you feel finally about what happened today?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Well Piers, as somebody who was in public service for 35 years, our hearts and prayers go out to the loved ones of those who lost loved ones today.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "And is there anything that can be done in light of what's happened to improve security at places like LAX?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well Piers let me just say, that's a silly idea.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "What was your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "They say that about everything.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Some of the last few weeks, has it been as I said a comedian's dream?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Well I think the country in general is on a decline.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "I mean, you've covered this for so long, what do you think?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "You know, I'm not a big fan of scapegoating.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "I mean should somebody carry the can for the fact that the system has started so badly?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Well no, well yeah ever if it's actually scapegoating.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Ever?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "When she says we're going to bring you the A Team.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Who knows all the details, why get rid of her now to make the situation worse?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Well that's absolutely true, there's no defense for that I would never defend him on that.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Where was the A Team before?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Not credible and not excusable.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Is it really credible what that the President, who's massive legacy may be based around this, didn't know anything about it being problematic?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Exactly, you know, well if I use the clicker will I get another, you know.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "This is grand dad not knowing how to use the Internet right?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Now I've warmed you nicely to the top of the pot and the boiling center was coming out of you.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "That's the patriotic thing to do about a program that is trying to bring healthcare to people in this country who don't' have it?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Oh it's always -- perfect, perfectly wrong, you know, right it's the Democrats who only care about power that's right.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Well you might (inaudible), what do you make of her arguments?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "It probably will be.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Could it be him against Chris Christie?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "You know, if it's the primary voters who vote every time, I think it will be Ted Cruz.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "And who will prevail?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "You know, we don't know until he became President what it would mean.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Well yeah, what it would mean for America and for America's reputation do you think?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Well because first of all we're the gun (ph) in the country.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "What does this say about American culture that those two issues, people are very happy to move with times and change but one is culturally, apparently irrevocable?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Probably not in my lifetime.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Will it ever change?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "No I would hardly call it speedy.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Are you surprised at the speed with which both those things have moved in public opinion?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Absolutely, I mean that's what happens when a tipping point is reached with the states, I think that's what will happen with gay marriage and probably some day with marijuana itself.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Could you see a time in 30, 40 years in America where issues like gay marriage, marijuana became Federal issues or just a Federal Law encompassing the whole of America?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "No I don't think it has, it's because people always found it so easy to get weed.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "Well I thought it moved quite quickly you don't think it has?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "You're asking me to choose between my children?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "George Carlin did.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Will you literally you do stand up till the day they carry you out in the box?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "It would be a great way to go.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Would that be your dream exit from life?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "AHER: Well I'm hoping Ray Kurzweil is correct and I'll live forever.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "DO you think you'll live to be a 100?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Well it does matter because when we didn't use to have these kind of places where you could retreat to your, you know, ghettoization of thinking, public discourse was the better for it because you had to hear a conflicting idea and now you don't.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Right but does it matter?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "If that doesn't get what I'm saying nothing will.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Wrestling?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "I was watching the other day, it's really not even coming back to me.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "You couldn't even remember that happening?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "I love Jay Leno, I'm on a bash with Jay Leno.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "What do you make Jay Leno?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Well of course a lot of it is that.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Why does he get such a hard wrath from other comedians, is it a jealousy?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Because what I understand I mean incredibly nice, charming?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "He doesn't have someone talking in the ear of the network executive like the other guys do saying, \"Get rid if Jay, he's too old.\"", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "He does it himself right?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "131101pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Do you have an agent?", "qSentId": 523}]